Hello friends I am Xyram Chandrashekhar
Ugale welcome you to my Share Market YouTube channel.
We will see the quarter
3 results of HDFC, ICICI LBD, ICICI
Securities and LNT Technology, these are the four
big companies.  Ah, almost everyone, whether
in the stock market or not,
knows about these four companies.  HDFC Bank is the biggest bank in
India.  Its result was declared today
and it showed a net profit of Rs 16372 crore in the
October to December quarter, meaning
they have made a jump of 33.5%.
Now the net profit of Rs 16,372
crore is almost in line with the market estimate, which
means it is
slightly less than the estimate of Rs 16,427 crore, but the net
profit is good.  Now we will look at its PE
ratio because the profit has been good.  Whether you
buy it or not.  So the PE
ratio is 23.  Should be around 15.   The
PE ratio is also fine.  If you
look at almost all the companies, the PE ratio is very
high.  Now the PB ratio is 4.38.
What does the PB ratio indicate?  Valuation is the
price to book ratio of the company,
we are paying 4.38 times that.
Now if
we look at it here, the red flag
is low.  Is good.  The entry point is average.   I
mean, uh, almost, it's good for profit.
Ah profitability is high.  High profitability
means that there are high chances
of making profits and the performance is low,
valuation is high, growth is low.
The valuation is high right now, which I told you is that
you are paying three times.  Income
higher than industry higher than industry
revenue growth.  Industry revenue growth
is 12.0.  So HDFC 15.09 increase
market share.  Its market share increased
and earlier it was 22.74.  It is now 26.16.  It means
growth.  Lower than industry net income.
Net income is the revenue, the
sales, whatever is left after subtracting expenditure,
whatever is left after subtracting capital operating expenditure is
net income.  Its net income is
less than the interest.  Ok?  Revenue if
you we have already seen.  We have already
seen the profit.  So
what's there to see?  There is cash flow and
if you look at the cash flow, there is working capital, the
difference between assets and liabilities, but the
liabilities of the bank are more
because it takes money from others and
gives it to a third person, so this
liability is more.  Therefore, if you
look at it, you will find almost minus for banks.
But the rest is free cash flow.
Free cash flow is
what remains after capital and operating expenditure.
So this
is also fine.  Holding: If you look at it,
what is the holding?  Decrease in holding:
Promoter holding: The promoter has
decreased the holding and the rest is low
pledge holding.
Currently, the total promoter holding is showing 0.00% in this,
for institutional 52.30
and retailer and other 16.89,
so this is the peer competition, if we see then in
P comparison, sorry if you
see in pay comparison, then only ICICI Bank has low P ratio.
Rest of the banks are at number three
but HDFC Bank also has the highest PB ratio.
Now we
will see the technical analysis and where it would be right to buy HDFC Bank.
If you see HDFC Bank now, it is
going upside by setting higher losses.
So holding this line he is going upside.
So we should have said goodbye here.
Well, he went too far.  Now if we have to buy,
it has touched a range many times.
If one touches a range too much,
that range becomes weak.  So
after the breakout, if it comes back to this range
around 10720 then you can buy it.
This was from HDFC.  Now we will
look at the next one of ICICI LBRD.
ICICI Lombard: Now we will see the results of ICICI.
ICICI Quarter 3 Premium Income to Rise
15%
Combined Ratio to Be Elevated
If we also see the Lab,
Net Profit of Rs 57 crore for the October to
December has increased by 44% year on year.
So its result is also good.  Net earned
premium is the measure of income earned by the
insurance company less the expenses
associated with the policy.  Meanwhile the company's
gross direct premium income is likely to come
in at ₹351
crore.  Now it has increased by 13% year on year.  So,
this is a good result.  Now we will
look at the fundamentals of ICICI and Lombard.
What will we look at first in fundamentals
?  PE Ratio.  What is PE ratio
?  Is 38.46.  PB ratio 6.47 means we are
paying a higher amount for it.  Now if
we look at the financials, you
can see here that there is a low flag.  Ok?   The
entry point is average.  even do.   The
profitability is high.  even do.
Performance is low.  The valuation is high.
That was told by the PB ratio.  Growth
is low.  Now Higher Than Industrial Revenue
Growth.  Its revenue growth is higher than the industry.
Decrease market share.  The market
share was earlier 3.61.  It's 1.53 now.  Meaning
which can be called participation.  Higher than
industry net income.  But its net income is
more than the industry.  So this is
known.  We have seen that the net profit has
increased by 13% and the dividend per share is
also up by 10% i.e. ₹10.  EPS has also increased.
Cash Flow Now we will look at cash flow.
If you look at the cash flow, the net change in cash is
minus here.  But here their free cash
flow is quite large and
their capital expenditure is 120.  He is also big.
So we will see this in the balance sheet.
If you look at the balance sheet, the total
asset is Rs 55000 crore.  So the total
liability is 44000, so if we look at it, the
balance sheet is also fine.  Lower than
industrial day to equity ratio Day to
equity ratio is good for this.  The company is
much lower than the industry.  So this is a very
positive point.  Lower the industrial
current ratio.  Current ratio is current
assets divided by current liabilities.  This
is much lower than the industry.  Now
we will see its holding.
If you look at the holding, the total
promoter holding is constant in six months.
It means okay.  Low pledge
promoter holding is also fine.  He has
not kept any promoter holding in this.  It is
not mortgaged.
Rest if you look at it, promoter holding
is 48% and retail has 11%.  The rest is
mostly with foreign institutions and mutual funds.  So
this is also correct in that sense.  Its balance sheet
is fine.  Profit also went away.  The company
is also good.  The company is also to be considered.  Ah, this
is a very well known company.  If you want to say goodbye now,
you can see it here.  Its
high is 10600 sorry 10674.  Now the
company has created a double bottom here, as you can see after the gap up opening.  There has just been an
upside.  It is trading above the 50 EMA.
But if you look at the weekly, the
RSI is down here right now.  Down, this
trend line is touching here once, twice and the third time.
If you buy here around 1352, then
if it comes down then you have to
average here near 1268.  And the first
target is 1491 second 164.
So you can buy here because
it will go upside only in zigzag motion.  So this kind of
length is also fine.  Now we will next
look at
LAT
LTTS technology and see its fundamentals.
Then here we will see LTTS.
Currently LTTS Technology Service Limited
reported net profit of Rs 336.2
crore for the quarter from
October to December.  This growth is 13.3% from Rs
296 crore to Rs 336 crore.
What does growth mean?  If
your growth is only ₹100 every year, then that growth is
profit, otherwise it is not considered growth.
But every year you are increasing it from 100 to 110, 120,
then next year it increases a little more, so that is
called growth.  When growth
is increasing, it means that the company is doing good work
and the company is focusing on its growth.
So this was the growth, so we
will directly see what is PE ratio PB ratio?
Because nowadays technology is very popular,
we should pay more attention to technology.
Technology Services
Limited offers design analysis,
prototyping and testing. Its PE
ratio is more than 45.  The PB ratio
is also 11.59.  We are paying him 11 times more money.
Now
we will see its fundamentals.   If we
look at the P and PB ratio, we are paying 11 times
if we buy at this price
and if you see its buying price there, it was actually
here, when
this harmonic pattern
AB CD does retracement, then the golden ratio which is around 5,
here
its buying was around 4100.  Now look here, it is
giving retrace after achieving the target.  So if you have to
buy, you should buy around 4854
and the target will be
5634 and further.  This is the technical analysis of
LTTS.  Now
if you look at the report of ICIC Securities, the
net profit stands at Rs 465 crore
in the quarter ending December 2023, marking
a jump of 67% as compared to the year.
Now if you look at the report of ICICI Securities, the
red flag is low.  The entry point
is average.  The profitability is high.  Growth low,
valuation high.